(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-02T20:28:22.918741",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
金星の隅で
In the corner of Venus,
惑星はグルグル回る
the planets spin round and round.
電波の記録
Records of radio waves
エコーが返ってきた
echo back to me.
これで何回だ
How many times has this been?
遠くの空で
Far away in the sky,
あなたに恋をしたんだ
I fell in love with you.
届かないこと
Even though I know
わかっているのに
it will never reach you...
ああ あなたに会いたいな
Ah, wanting to see you right now—
って気持ちがループする
that feeling loops endlessly.
頭が どうにかなりそうだ
My head is about to go crazy.
それ以外考えられない
I can't think about anything else.
ああ 今すぐ会いたいな
Ah, wanting to see you right now—
めくる日々をループする
an old routine loops endlessly.
この周回軌道上に
On this orbital path,
あなたがいなくても
even if you are not here,
そこに大体愛があるだけ
there is basically just love there.
There is basically just love there.
声をたどって何年だ
Following your voice, how many years has it been?
炎上線に消えていく
Vanishing into the line of fire.
このままパッと忘れられたら
If I could just forget it all like this...
楽だろうな
How easy that would be...
触れられないのに見えてしまってどうしようもないや
but I can see you though I can't touch you.
近くて遠いあなただ
You are so close yet so far away.
わかってるよ
I know that.
ああ それでも会いたいな
Ah, even so, I want to see you.
て何度もループする
That thought loops over and over.
心が あなたでなっている
My heart is made entirely of you—
それだけが確かだ
that is the only thing I know for sure.
それだけでいいよ
That alone is enough.
ああ 星が回るように 僕らはずつとループする
Ah, like stars spinning, we loop endlessly.
想いが 軌道を描いている あなただけをよ
Our feelings trace an orbit—just you alone.
ああ 今すぐ会いたいな
Ah, wanting to see you right now—
て命がループする
that life force loops endlessly.
この周回軌道上に
On this orbital path,
あなたがいなくても
even if you are not here,
それ以外を求めない
I cannot yearn for anything else.
そこに大体愛があるだけ
There is basically just love there.
はあ、すごい悲しいことがあったの。
Haah, something really sad happened.
慰めてほしいな。
I want you to comfort me.
…っていうのは、嘘ぴょん！
...That's a lie, pyon!
何食べてるの？
What are you eating?
おいしー！トワ様にもちょうだい！
Ooh! Give Towa-sama some too!
あーん
Nom, nom...
うん、おいしかった！てきゅう！
Mm, delicious! Thank you!
こやみー！
Koyami!
みんな、トワ様どこにいると思う？
Everyone, where do you think Towa-sama is?
どこにいる？あ、
Where is she?
どこにいると思う？当てた？
Where do you think she is? Did you guess?
あ、
Ah.
や、
Yaww-
やーん
じゃあびっくりしちゃうよ！
Then let's surprise you!
ぱあ！ここでしたー！
Ta-da! Right here!
みたー？
See?
わかった？みんな！
Did you get it, everyone?
いくよ！ほい、どん！じゃあ！
Here we go! Hoi, don!
やーい、こやみー！ホライミョウキセの…
Yay! Koyami! Houraimyouki's...
トワ様です！やーい！
Towa-sama is here! Yay!
やったー！や、うれしい！どう？見えてる？どう？
Yay, I'm so happy! How are you doing? How?
かわいい？ちょっとコメントとか見よっかな。
Cute? Let me check the comments and stuff.
どう？
How?
天使？おい、天使じゃねえ、悪魔だよ！
Angel? Oi, I'm not an angel, I'm a demon!
悪魔、悪魔！
Demon, demon!
悪魔じゃなくて天使。おー！
I'm a demon, not an angel!
ちょっと悪魔なんですからの、
Wait, I'm a demon, you know!
さっきの悪魔的所業も見たでしょ？
You saw that "Akuma-teki Shogyo" earlier, right?
ちゃんとやってますよ。お。
I'm doing it properly. Oh.
お！ピピがいっぱい出てきたー！
Oh, lots of pipi are coming out!
でね、さっきのね、惑星ループなんだけど、あ、コクチュ！
And you know, that "wakusei loop" from earlier... Ah, Kokuchu!
あのるってるってるってるってっていうかけ声はね、4期生のみんなにお願いしたんだー！
That "rutturuttruttruttu" shouting was a request for everyone in Horkisei, right?
どうだった？わかった？
How was it? Did you get it?
わかった？
Did you get it?
すごい、やっぱ久しぶりにさ、踊ってみたからさ、
You know, it's been a while since I danced, so...
トワももともと踊りって好きなんだけど、運動音痴だから全然やってなくて、人前に見せるっていう
I actually love dancing, but since it's a fitness gym, I haven't been doing it at all, and showing it in front of people...
レベルじゃないからさ、ぎゃっ ともう
that level, you know, so I was super...
いや、ちょっとかわいい。ちょっと見た？
Hey, it's kind of cute. Did you see?
わあ、でっかい！
Whoa, huge!
みて、みて、どう？どう、これ？
Look, look, how is it? How is this?
どう、てか男子もどうだった？かわいかった？
How about the guys too? Was it cute?
やー！みて！
Yay! Look!
ピピだ、ピピ！かわいいでしょ、ピピ！
Pipi, oh Pipi! They're so cute, Pipi!
かわいいー！やー！
So cute! Yay!
あのね、悪魔のね、やりもるあるんです、やりも。
You know, demons have their own ways too. Ways!
てぃてぃるてぃるてぃるてぃるー！
Tiri-tiri-tiri-tiru-tuu!
ほら、ほら！超悪魔らしいやろ？
See? Super-akuma-like, right?
トワ様マジ悪魔！
Towa-sama's maji akuma!
マジ大悪魔！
Maji dai akuma!
ぷぷーん！
Puwuun!
これじゃな、きみたちを天使って言ったらきみたちをね、こう刺しますから！
See? If you call us angels, we'll pierce you!
あ、ごめん。先端恐怖症の人ごめん！
Ah, sorry, I meant the cutting-edge show people, sorry!
ごめん、目をつぶって、じゅっしゅー！い！
Sorry, close your eyes! Good!
すごい！みんな見てる？みんな見てる？トワのこと見てる？やー！
Amazing! Everyone, are you watching? Look at Towa-sama! Yay!
なに、どんだけ？トワ様もテンション上がっちゃって、もう本当に！
Really, how much? Even if Towa-sama gets too excited, seriously!
これね、これでピピを、しゅばーんってやります。いきます。
You know, with this, we'll give Pipi a shuban! Here we go!
うわ、しゅばーん！
Whoa, shuban!
わあ、待って！
Whoa, wait!
なに あいつ？
What's with that guy?
え、こわっ！
Whoa, scary!
なになに？
What's going on?
なにこれ？ 最初からなんだよ
What is this? It's been like that since the start.
なに？片隅だけ？
What? Just in the corner?
きたー！
It's here!
なに？なんでこいつの中、結婚式の入場この中……
Why is this guy's wedding entrance in here...
だ、誰来ないで！
D-Don't come closer!
あ、近付かないで！
Ah, don't get near me!
あ、死んだ。
Ah, it died.
これわな、これ眷属だから
You see, this is a familiar.
悪魔のことさ、悪魔じゃなくて天使って呼ぶ眷属を。目標はね、カツを入れますから、今日カツを入れます。
We call familiars angels rather than demons. Our goal is to give them a pep talk, so today I'll give them a pep talk.
眷属は、あ、天使じゃ？あ、
The familiar is, oh, an angel? Oh,
もう一回立ってもろて
Please stand up again.
眷属は、天使じゃない！
The familiar is not an angel!
悪魔だぁ！
It's a demon!
という空気が流れた。あ、倒れた。
Such an atmosphere flowed through. Ah, it fell down.
立って？
Get up?
あ、あ、立って、眷属よしよし
Ah, ah, get up. Good familiar, good boy/girl.
ワールドワイド眷属よしよし
Worldwide familiar, good job.
いつもありがとう！
Thank you as always!
ぎゅ、あ、ぎゅ、ぎゅ、
Hug, ah, hug, hug,
バイバイ、もう帰っていいよ、じゃあな。
Bye-bye, you can go home now, see ya.
バイバイ、ありがとう！あ、きた！
Bye-bye, thank you! Ah, it's back!
どんな？えー、いいよ。
How is it? Um, it's good.
トワ様の体の、体のことね、体のね、体のボディを見てほしい、体のボディを。
I want you to look at Towa-sama's body, my body's details.
バイバイ、
Bye-bye,
どんだけいるの？
How many are there?
トワ様のボディを見てほしいんだ。
I want you to look at Towa-sama's body.
てっちゃん、下から見てもらって。
Tet-chan, please look from below.
見て、足！靴可愛いでしょう？
Look at my feet! Aren't these shoes cute?
マミーがデザインした靴だけど、すごい可愛いでしょう？
They're shoes designed by Mommy, but aren't they super cute?
後ろもね、ほら、こんな感じ！すごくおしゃれじゃない？
And the back too, look, like this! Isn't it super stylish?
で、そっからだんだん上に上がってもろて。
And then gradually move up.
てっ？
T...?
見て、絆創膏。トワ様よく転んじゃうから、べったりべったりよ。
Look, the band-aid. Towa-sama trips a lot, so it's plastered all over.
いやそんな、アップしないで、恥ずかしいから！
Hey, don't zoom in like that, it's embarrassing!
ちゃんと、もう早く上上がって！
Come on, hurry up and go higher!
で、見てこの太もも。いい感じでしょう？
And look at these thighs. Pretty nice, right?
この、なんだろう、この
This, I wonder, this
センシティブ、センシティブな太ももかも知れない。
Sensitive, these sensitive thighs perhaps.
長い、長い、長い、長い、長い、
Too long, long, long, long, long,
恥ずかしい、そんな見せないで！
Embarrassing, don't show that!
では、へそピアス！
And now, belly button piercing!
あ、ぷりぷり、これしっぽ！
Ah, plump, this is the tail!
これしっぽ可愛いでしょう、これ。トワのしっぽピアスもついてるの。
Isn't this tail cute? Towa's tail has a piercing too.
で、トワのおしりはこうね、これこう
And Towa's butt is like this, like this
これ、実はハートのね、穴が空いてて、ハートの穴からしっぽが出てんの。
Actually, it has a heart-shaped hole, and the tail comes out through the heart-shaped hole.
ちょっと、おしりアップしすぎ！見てしっぽもほら、こここれ
Wait, too much butt zoom! Look at the tail too, see, right here
どう？見て、あと爪ネイル！
How is it? Look, and nail art!
ネイル可愛いでしょう？ピカピカ。
Aren't the nails cute? Shiny.
で、へそピアス。
And belly button piercing.
で、で、で、
And, and, and,
で、お洋服でーん！
And ta-da, the outfit!
で、かの、これ何？キーホルダー。
And, what is this? A keychain.
お洋服についてる、「towa」って書いてあるの。
Attached to the clothes, it says "towa".
可愛いでしょう、これもね、みんなにあげたいけど、あげなーい！
Isn't it cute? I'd love to give this to everyone too, but I won't!
私専用！えへへ
Just for me! Ehehe
えへへ、ありがとう！
Ehehe, thank you!
お耳、お耳見て。
My ears, look at my ears.
帽子も？
Want the hat too?
カエルの帽子も？
Want the frog hat too?
このピンバッチほしい？
Want this pin badge?
ピンバッチほしい？
Want a pin badge?
ピンバッチはね...
The pin badge is...
ちょっと考えとくわ。
I'll think about it.
考えとくね。
I'll think about it, okay?
帽子はね、実は取れるんだよ。
The hat actually comes off, you know.
行くよ？ ちょっと待っててね。
Ready? Just wait a second.
もうちょいで。
Almost there.
てれーん！
Ta-da!
じゃあーん！
Tada!
あ、待って、こう。
Ah, wait, like this.
帽子も取れます！
The hat comes off too!
なんかすごい あれだけど。
It looks kind of amazing, though.
かわいいでしょ、これ。
Cute, right?
投げれるんだよ。
You can throw it, you know.
行くよ？
Here it goes?
ぴょーん！ ああ！
Boing! Ah!
じゃあーん！
Ta-da!
どう？
How is it?
あ、こっちだ。
Ah, this way.
こうだ。
Like this.
いいでしょ、これ。
Pretty good, right?
ほら。ふーん。
Look. Hmph.
じゃあーん！
Ta-da!
ちょっと、ちょ...
Wait, wai...
かぶって。
Put it on!
じゃあな！
See ya!
このあとは、ちょっと またかくれんぼの続きをやりますから。
After this, we're going to continue the hide-and-seek.
この、このトワ様の秘密のな、教会でかくれんぼするから。
So we're doing hide-and-seek in Towa-sama's secret church here.
みんな、トワがどこにいるか当ててね！
Everyone, guess where Towa is!
行くよ？
Ready?
はーい！
Okay!
じゃあね！ ちょっとおまちよ。
Bye-bye! Wait a moment.
どこに隠れよっかなー？
Where should I hide?
こっちかなー？
Over here?
こっち？ でもお...
Here? But...
隠れんぼ、羽を、はい。どうぞ。
Hide-and-seek, wings, yes. Here you go.
あ、どうぞ ここにいます。
Ah, here I am.
トワ様を探せ！
[Find Towa-sama!]
ぽん、ぽん。
Pon, pon.
わかる？
Can you tell?
どこにいるか？
Where am I?
どこだろー？ コメントみよー。
Where is it? Let's check the comments.
どこ？
Where?
わかる？
Can you tell?
わかるわかる？
Can you, can you?
ここだ？
Here?
あ、ここだ！
Ah, here!
ここだ、ここだ！
Here, here!
あ、当たってる！
Ah, you got it!
当たってる人いる！
Some people got it!
じゃあ正解見せておこっかなー。
Well, I'll show you the correct answer.
正解は、こちらでしたー！
The correct answer was right here!
やー！ 分かった？
Yay! Did you figure it out?
どこにいたか分かった？
Did you know where I was?
ここ、の入り口にいましたー！
I was right here at the entrance!
どーん！
Boom!
よし。
Alright.
じゃあ、その次また行っちゃいますよー！
Well then, we're heading to the next one!
じゃあね、次も当ててくださいねー！
Well then, make sure to guess the next one too!
えー、どこにしようかなー。
Ugh, where should I hide?
えっと、ここ？
Um, here?
ここにしよう。
Let's do here.
ここでいっか。
Here is fine.
ここ？
Here?
どこにしよう？
Where should I?
さあさあさあさあ、どこにいるでしょうかー？
Now, now, now, where could I be?
これね、カメラの位置にも注目だね。
Now, pay attention to the camera position.
メテメテローアングルなんだけど。
It's a super low angle though.
ということは、結構下にいるかなーみたいな。
That means, probably pretty low down or something.
ていう感じだと思う。
That's the kind of vibe.
わかるかな？ めちゃめちゃ激ムズかもしれない。
Can you figure it out? It might be super crazy hard.
あ、やばい！これについてくるんだ、トワのあとに。やー！
Ah, yikes! It's following right behind Towa. Yay!
あ、やばいバレる。
Ah, crap, I'll get caught.
おい、やめろ！
Hey, stop it!
あ、やばい、これはバレた。これバレてしまった、眷属に。
Ah, crap, I've been found out. I've been exposed to my minions.
じゅ、ここー！
He, here!
ちょっと、なんでそ... 来ないでよ！
Wait, why ar... Don't come over here!
あ、ここは難しかった？
Ah, was this one difficult?
ま、ま、ま、ちょっと、こいつ、こいつは誰な...
W-w-wait, who is this guy...
いまの... 来るな。
...right now... don't come.
もう次、もう次行っちゃおっか、ね。
Let's just move on to the next one, right?
もうこのまま次行っちゃうから、はい、もう次ー！
We're going straight to the next one, yup, next one!
これはね、あ、こんなとこ、
This is, oh, somewhere like this,
こんな感じ。
this kind of vibe.
は？
Huh?
はい、どこでしょうーか？
Alright, where could it be?
お、え、正解あったわ！すごい！正解あったわ！行くぞ！
Oh, wow, someone got it right! Amazing! Someone got it right! Here we go!
えと、これは簡単なのかな？逆に。
Um, is this easy? Or rather, the opposite?
ちょっと…
Wait...
世界発表は…どーん！
And now, the world reveal... Boom!
初見。
First try.
あ、あ、あ、あ、あ…
Ah, ah, ah, ah...
ここ？ここだーい！
Here? Right here!
ちょっとさ、トワ様3Dやったのが嬉しくてさ
You know, I'm so happy I finally got my 3D model,
いちいちポーズ取っちゃうね。
I keep striking poses all the time.
じゃあね、最後、もう一番最後の、ここだよ！
Well then, finally, for the very last one, it's right here!
トワ様をさがせ！ラストになります。
Find Towa-sama! This is the final one.
あー、トワ様、ちょっと休憩したいな。
Ah, Towa-sama wants to take a little break.
休憩したいから、ここにしようかな。
Since I want to take a break, I'll choose here.
ここにしよ、大変なんだよ、ここ来るの大変なんだよ、ここが。
It's so tough getting up here, coming all the way up here is really hard.
ここ…
Here...
ここわかる？
Do you know where this is?
これ、あ、ちょっと、あ、うー、これ以外にちょっと疲れるんだけど。
Man, oh, this is actually pretty exhausting, though.
どうかな？あ、ごめん、見えてん？見えてる？
How is it? Oh wait, can you see me? Can you see me?
ちょっとし、視野ん、し、そこは…
Let's see, my field of view...
ツールー、あ、ちょっと待って、あ、ツールー、
Tooroo, oh wait, oh, tooroo...
これめちゃめちゃきつい！あー、早く上さ、もこたんでいいです！トワ様、足が死んじゃいます。
This is super tough! Ah, hurry up, up there—Mokotan is fine! Towa-sama's legs are gonna die.
あー、足つる、足つる、足つる、やったー！ここでしたー！
Ah, my legs are cramping, cramping, cramping! Yay! It was right here!
ふう、足つる、ふう、ふう、トワ様がジャンプマスターだ。
Phew, leg cramp... Phew, phew. Towa-sama is the Jump Master.
うぴょーん！
Boing!
あー、どうだった？みんな分かった？全部、分かりました？
Ah, how was it? Did everyone figure it out? Did you understand all of them?
トワ様、ちょっとでも、だんだんと、はあはあっていきぎれ、いきぎれ症状を兼ね兼ねてる。
Towa-sama, even so, gradually... huff huff, I'm feeling out of breath.
もうちょっとね、大変な感じなんだけどね、楽しい！
It feels pretty tough, but it's fun!
いぇーい！今、Twitterのトレンドも、世界のトレンドも、「これだって」、あ、こっちだ、「これだって」って！
Yay! Right now, both Twitter trends and world trends are saying "This is it!" — oh wait, over here, "This is it!" —
うちも、「こっちだって」！
Me too, "It's over here!" —
ちょ、ちょ、ちょっと、こ、ここここ、あ、ちょっと、こっち、こっち、こっち！
Wait, wait, wait, right here, right here, oh wait, this way, this way, this way!
スクショいっぱい撮って、Twitterでつぶやいてなー！
Take lots of screenshots and tweet them out on Twitter!
あ、ちょっと待って、トワ様さ、1個だけやりたいのがあって、ちょっと全身映してもらえますか？
Ah, wait a second, Towa-sama has one more thing she wants to do. Could you show my whole body?
ちょっと、これだけよろしくね！すしざんまい！
Um, please just do this much! Sushizanmai!
これやんないとさ、これやんないとだめ。来いよ！
If I don't do this, if I don't do this, it's no good. Come on!
よーし、はい、ということで、以上はね、こちら、あの、トワ様の「さがせ」コーナーでした！じゃあね、次のコーナーへ、レッツゴー！
Alright, yep! So that concludes the Towa-sama "Find Me" corner! Well then, let's go to the next corner, let's go!
あ、の、前に、トワ様、ごめん、忘れがち。あのね、悪魔になるための勉強でまたちょっとしたから、そちらをもう一回、また別のも見たいな。そちらの、トワまで？ドン！
Ah, before that, Towa-sama, sorry, I tend to forget. Um, you know, studying to become a devil, I did a bit of that earlier, so I want to see another one. That Towa-ma—? Bam!
かなたんの手裏剣をドーナツに変える
[Title: Turning Kanata's shuriken into donuts]
かなたんの天使の輪でフリスビー
[Title: Turning Kanata's angel ring into a frisbee]
うははははは！しっとがゴミのようだ！ふははははははは！
Uwahahahaha! Jealousy is like trash! Fuhahahahahaha!
屋上から「小せえ、見ろ！人がゴミのようだ！」と一人で言う
Saying "So tiny, look! People are like trash!"
alone from the rooftop.
トワ様でもできる！悪魔的所業
Even Towa-sama can do it! Demonic Deeds
あ、久しぶり！元気？また今度遊ぼうね。またねー！
Ah, long time no see! How are you?
Let's hang out again. Bye-bye!
人の背中に特売シールや値札シールを貼る
Putting bargain stickers or
price tags on people's backs
トワ様でもできる！悪魔的所業
Even Towa-sama can do it! Demonic Deeds
はっ
Huh?
とーさまのお部屋にー？とーさまのー？
In Towa-sama's room?
Towa-sama's...
でっかい！とーさまのお部屋がさー
It's huge! Towa-sama's room is...
めっちゃお洒落でしょ？とーさまのお部屋をみんなにね、紹介しまーす！
Super stylish, right?
I'll introduce Towa-sama's room to everyone!
あ、見て！すごい綺麗な...感じ。
Ah, look! Such a pretty... vibe.
このね、鏡をね、見てね、とーさまいつもね、身だしなみチェックしてんの。きゅきゅっ。
Look at this mirror, Towa-sama is
always checking her appearance here. *Qyu-qyu!*
あとね、額縁にね、いろんなの飾ってあるんだよ。ちょっと見て？どぅー！
And, you know, there are all sorts of things
framed here. Take a look, *do-sh!*
じゃーん！これ、これ掛け軸って言うか、とーがね、ライオン描いて、ルルドママの絵だったんだけど、
Ta-da! This is like a hanging scroll—
Towa drew a lion, though it was Luludo-mama's art,
描いて、掛け軸って言うか、塗ってくれたやつ！塗ってくれたやつ！いいでしょ？
she colored it—well, a hanging scroll,
the one she painted for me! Isn't it nice?
えっと、あ、全部できるのかな？ぱぱっ。
Um, can I show all of them?
*Papap!*
じゃーん！や、やっぱり上手だな。塗りがあの、線画がしっかりしてるから塗りもやっぱり、こういう、こうごうしい、こうごうしい感じになるんだろな。
Ta-da! Man, it really is good.
Since the line art is so solid, the coloring
turns out so majestic, you know.
じゃあね、次真ん中のね、とこ。真ん中の絵。
Now, next, the middle place.
The picture in the middle.
これ、ルリ先生が描いてくれた、ホロライブ4期生の集合絵だよ！これいいでしょ？これすごい好き、これ。
This is a group illustration of Hololive
4th Gen drawn by Ruri-sensei! Isn't this great?
I love this so much, this.
これ手って、手ってだ？これ好き。でもとーもなんか、じーん、じーん、みんなのりれ受け取ったよっていう感じよ。
These hands... these hands, right? I love this.
It also makes Towa feel like she received
everyone's feelings.
で、こっち一番端っこは、一番端っこは、ママがとーのタペストリーで描いてくれた...
And, the one on the far end here,
the far end, mama drew for Towa's tapestry...
ちょっとオフのとー様。オフのとー様、オフ様...オフ様、なの。かわいいでしょ？でも見ないだな、そんなに恥ずかしいから。
A slightly off-duty Towa-sama.
Off-duty Towa-sama, off-sama...
Cute, right? But don't look too closely, it's embarrassing.
とは、最後もう一つ、もう一つ飾ってて、はい、こちら！これね、トワがデビューした時に、まずこれルルドママがね描いてくれたの！これもママが描いてくれたの！で、今日ママがね配信、この配信する前に見てるよ、がんばってねって言ってくれたんだ。嬉しいなー。
And finally, there's one more displayed here,
yes, right here! When Towa debuted,
Luludo-mama drew this for me first!
Mama said before stream: "I'm watching!" So happy.
ま、そんな感じお部屋は。
Well, that's what the room's like.
じゃね、さあここからはね、なんだなんだ、めちぇめちぇめちぇめちぇ！大事です！もうスクショを撮るならここしかないっていうコーナー、ま、ここしかないわけでもないんだけど、ま、ここしかないって言わせてもらうというコーナーです！シートリな、シートリジェスチャーをやりにいきたいと思います！
Now then, from here on, wait, what is it?
It's super important! This is the corner
where if you're taking screenshots, it has to be here—
well, let's just say it has to be!
I want to do the C-tri gesture!
こちら！共感してくれるよね？共感してくれるよね？できないなんて言わせないよ！
Right here! You sympathize, right?
You sympathize, right? Don't tell me you can't!
こちらになります！タイトル名は「こちら！」へらって言うなよって言わないでくださいな、これな。ルールは簡単、今からトワ様の、あの左右にね、左右にねイラストが出てきて、それがシートリになるようにトワ様がジェスチャーをします。
Here it is! Title is "Right Here!"
Don't say "don't parry" or whatever, okay?
Rules are simple: illustrations appear on my left and right,
and Towa-sama poses to form a C-tri.
トワ様がやってるジェスチャーが何なのか、視聴者のみんなが考えるクイズになります！なんかどんだけみたいな、あはは、どんだけみたいなつだ。まあ、わかってね。
It's a quiz for viewers to guess what gesture
Towa-sama is doing! Like "How much is that?"
haha, something like that. Well, figure it out.
まね、1問目、もうすごい簡単なのを用意したので、こちらをじゃあ、やってみましょう！ででーん。あ、めちゃくちゃ上手ですね
Well, for the first question, I prepared a super
simple one, so let's try this! *Ta-da!*
Ah, that's ridiculously good.
これ？
This?
まあ、いけますよ。
Well, I can do this.
ジェスチャー。
Charades.
なんか喋れないのもなんかドキドキするね。
It's kind of nerve-wracking not being able to talk.
うん、こうよ。
Yeah, like this.
こうじゃない？
Isn't it like this?
あ！あ！えっ！あっ、合ってる合ってる！すごいすごいすごい！
Ah! Ah! Eh! Ah, you got it, you got it! Amazing, amazing!
あ！
Ah!
合ってる合ってる！そうそう！
You got it, you got it! That's it!
正解はタヌキでした！わーい！
The answer was a tanuki! Yay!
ほら、ぽんぽんぽんぽん。
See, pon-pon-pon-pon.
タヌキふー！
Tanuki, whoo!
イエーイ！
Yay!
こんなことさ、ハハ、ハハって書いちゃうよ。
Writing things like "Haha, haha" like this.
じゃあな、じゃあ、第2問目いってみましょう！
Well then, let's go to the second question!
に！
Two!
あ、これめちゃくちゃ上手い、これ。
Ah, this is super good, this one.
これ、めちゃめちゃ上手いから、これ。これ！
Because this is super good, this. This!
これ、真ん中はこうですよう。
This, the middle is like this.
これめちゃめちゃだよ。
This is a mess.
これと、あと、これ。分かった？
This and, also, this. Did you get it?
これ、トワが何やってるか分かる？
Do you know what Towa is doing here?
トワが何やってるか分かる？
Do you know what Towa is doing?
これ事前、あのめちゃめちゃ直近で書いたんだけど、このイラストで。
I drew this beforehand, well, very recently, in this illustration.
トワのジェスチャーは何をやっかっていうのも全然知らされてなかったんだけど、
I wasn't told at all what Towa's gesture was supposed to be portraying, but...
運営さ、あなどり、あな、あな、あな、あなどりましたね。トワ様はこれが大好き。
Management, you underestimated me. Towa-sama loves this.
やば、シュート行っちゃった。
Oops, I went for a shoot.
え？ジェスチャーで分かってるけど、右側分かんない。これ分かるだろ、何でだよ！
Eh? I get the gesture, but I don't get the right side. You should get this, why!
何で分かんないの、これ。
Why don't you get this?
え、じゃあこれ、先週？
Eh, then this, last week?
あ、先週土曜のがヒント。
Ah, last Saturday's is the hint.
あ、先週土曜の、後ろ毛がヒントって言ってる、運営さんが。
Ah, management says the hint is last Saturday's back hair.
あ、そう。これは
Ah, right. This is...
あ！
Ah!
そうそうそうそうそう。
That's right, exactly.
え、これちゅ、おい。
Eh, this, hey.
こちら、正解は野球でしたー！
The answer for this one was baseball!
やー！
Yay!
これウナギだから。ウナギやろ。
Because this is an eel. It's an eel.
嘘でしょ？ミミズにしか見えん。ウナギ土の子。
No way? It only looks like an earthworm. Eel, tsuchinoko.
はあ？
Huh?
なんだよ、おい！
What is this, hey!
はい、じゃあ次行きまーす！
Alright, let's go to the next one!
次はな、これうまいから。やば、真ん中がトワのジェスチャーが難しい。次。
Next is, this is good. Oh no, the middle one, Towa's gesture is hard. Next.
これうま、これめちゃくちゃ上手くない、これ。
This is good, isn't this super good?
これが、これとこれだから、
This is this and this, so...
あ、こうよ、こうよ。
Ah, like this, like this.
やばい、シュートとか言っちゃいけないのか、ジェスチャーだから。
Oh no, I shouldn't say things like "shoot", since it's a gesture.
ああ、本当な。
Ah, seriously.
ああ。
Ah.
ちょ、わー！正解ある、正解ある！
Wait, wow! There's the answer, there's the answer!
わかった！あー！
I got it! Ah!
そう、正解はAPEXでした！
That's right, the answer was APEX!
これさ、そう、これサザエさんでしょ？サザエ、スイカ、だから、さ、
This, right, this is Sazae-san, right? Sazae, watermelon, so, sa...
さ、あ、さ、え、えで最後、スーで終わるからAPEX。
Sa, a, sa, e, e and ending with su, so APEX.
これレースのまでだったんだけど。
This was up to the race part, though.
これレースで、これ銃。分かった？
This is race, and this is gun. Did you get it?
分かりにくかった。
It was hard to understand.
じゃあ次行きまーす。
Well then, let's go to the next one.
これ、ツイッター運営さん、おい、運営！何考えてこの質問、これにしたんだよ。
This, Twitter management, hey, management! What were you thinking making this the question?
次はこっちだ。
Next is this one.
いや、まず天才的な絵。こっちこれ。
No, first of all, a genius-level drawing. This one here.
てことは、うんとな。
That means, let's see.
いや、表すとしたらこうなんだよな。
No, if I were to represent it, it's like this.
こう、こう、こう、と、これ、これとか。
Like this, this, this, and this, or this.
これから。
From here.
これ？これから？
This? From this?
あー、ちょちょちょ！正解ある！
Ah, wait wait wait! There's the answer!
やばい！これ、でしょ？
Oh no! This, right?
これと、あと
This and, also...
これこれこれこれこれこれ！これこれこれこれこれ！
This, this, this, this, this! This, this, this, this, this!
あ！
Ah!
そう！正解、すごい！正解ある！
That's right! Answer, amazing! There's the answer!
正解は、アサガオ、大空スバル！
The answer is, morning glory, Oozora Subaru!
これアサガオでしょ？アサガオを、大空スバル。
This is morning glory, right? Morning glory, Oozora Subaru.
ルーレット！
roulette!
これ、スバルちゃんのこれ、アヒルトゥー
This represents Aigis...
アヒルトゥー、これ救急車のピーポーって
and that's the ambulance going "pee-poo"!
ピーポー表したの！
Pee-poo, that's Subaru-chan!
えーどう？
What?
スバルちゃん？あ、スバルちゃん見てる？
Subaru-chan? Are you watching?
ほら。ほら。
Look, see?
だて、スバルちゃんのこと表して、こ、こ、これと、これ
That represents Subaru-chan!
これ！スバルちゃん！
Look, it's Subaru-chan!
これだよねー？ルーレットわかんない、うっそー！
Wait, I don't get the roulette. No way!
止まれよ。止まれよ。
Hold on, wait.
じゃ、な、なんと、なんと最後！最後の最後！
Wait, wait, the last one! The absolute last one!
な、なんてスバルちゃん突っ込んでる？
What is Subaru-chan saying?
おい！
Oi!
じゃ、スバルちゃん大好きー！
I love Subaru-chan!
スバルちゃん、大丈夫だよってチャットくれた！
She chatted: "Are you okay?"
ありがとー！
Thank you!
スバルちゃん、見てるー？
Subaru-chan, are you watching?
いえーい！
Yay!
ありがと、ございました！
Thank you very much.
じゃ、な、最後、な、最後。
Then, the last, the last one.
ラスト！行きます！ドドン！
Last one, let's go! Dodon!
これ。
This...
これの名前はね、苗字なしです。苗字。
This name has no last name! Last name?
苗字なし。これめちゃくちゃすごくないか？
No last name. Doesn't this look amazingly clever?
ほら。ほら。
Look. Look.
で、脇パイとな、だから間、間。間これ。
The armpit and the... Wait, in between, in between!
んと、んとね。
Hold on. Hold on, now.
んとね。
Wait, wait.
分かった、これ！分かった？あー、スバルちゃん分かってくれてる！
I got it! This! I got it?
ほら！ほら！
Ah, Subaru-chan figured it out!
Look! Look!
こっちが、ここ、き、ここで、こっちがわたあめ。
This side is "Coco" (here), and this side is "Wata-me" (cotton candy/Watame).
ココから始まってワで終わるから！先輩は...
It starts with "Coco" and ends with "Wa", so...
そう！公衆電話！
Ah, public telephone!
やったー！
Yay!
でも父さんもさ、全部結構えーうまくなかった？難しかった。
Towa-sama, did you think all of these were pretty clever?
どうだった？どうだった、トワの動きとか。
How was it? How was Towa's movement?
どう？
How?
あのさ、ここちんとわたちんの絵描くときに、あの、パイウツを、とりあえず母音母音にしとけばいっかって思って、めためた母音にした！
How, um, when I was drawing Coco-chin and Watame's illustrations, I thought, "Let's just make everything vowels and it'll be fine," so I made literally everything vowels!
母音にしないと、こらちえそとかさ、なん、なんで母音じゃないんですかっ！
If I didn't make them vowels, like "Kora-chaiso" and stuff...
ここちんとか言われちゃうか。
Coco-chin and others would say that.
どうだった？難しかった？
How was it? Was it difficult?
じゃあね、なんと、なんと。
Well then, next, next.
次、ミニコーナー、また最後だな！最後のな、悪魔的修行のミニコーナーを見てください！
Next is the mini-corner, and it's the last one! The last one! Please watch the autocratic training mini-corner!
いきます！ドドン！
Let's go! Dodon!
スマホの充電のコンセントをこっそり抜く
(She is sneaking up...)
悪魔的所業
Autocratic Training
あ、美味しそうですね。
Ah, it looks delicious!
あん、ん、美味しい！ありがとうございます！
Mm, delicious! Thank you very much!
試食コーナーを２周
(Taking supermarket food samples twice)
悪魔的所業
Autocratic Training
あ、ありがとうございます。
Ah, thank you very much.
唐揚げにレモンかけとくね！
I'll put some lemon on the fried chicken, okay?
唐揚げにレモン、かけとくね！！
"Putting lemon on fried chicken without asking!"
悪魔的所業
Autocratic Training
ポテチ食べた手で漫画べたべた触る
"Touching manga with greasy potato chip fingers"
悪魔的所業
Autocratic Training
トワ様でもできる！ 悪魔的所業
Even Towa-sama can do it! Devilish Deeds
見つめ合って恋をして
Staring at each other, falling in love,
無我夢中で追いかけて
chasing after you in a frenzy.
だけどもっと知りたくて
But wanting to know more,
メラメラしてる
burning up inside.
願うほど謎が増え
The more I wish, the more mysteries grow,
思うほど熱になる
the more I think, the hotter it gets.
だからもっと飛び込むの
So I'll dive in even more
未開の世界
into an unexplored world.
恋とか夢とか誰でも信じるけど
Everyone believes in love and dreams,
そこそこ攻めなきゃつまらないよ
but if you don't push yourself, it's no fun.
ギリギリ愛 いけないボーダーライン
Desperate love, the forbidden borderline,
難易度Gでも全て壊してみせる
even at difficulty G, I'll smash it all.
ギリギリマインド さらにGへと
Desperate mind, pushing even further to G,
意識は溶ける 体は制御不能 行っちゃうかもね
consciousness melts, body out of control, I might go!
ふざけあった友達と
With friends joking around,
求めあったあの人と
and that person we sought after,
また会える日のために
for the sake of meeting again,
キラキラしてる
I'm shining brightly.
光るほど影ができ
The more it shines, shadows form,
燃えるほど灰になる
the more it burns, it turns to ash.
走るほど見えてくる
The more I run, coming into view,
危ないライン
is a dangerous line.
自由も平和も望めば生まれるけど
Freedom and peace are born if you wish for them,
モタモタしてたら腐っちゃうよ
but if you dawdle, you'll rot away.
ギリギリ愛 危ないボーダーレス
Desperate love, a dangerous borderless,
非現実だね まだ加速しているよ
it's surreal, and it's still accelerating.
ギリギリマインド 限界点なら 塗り替えていい
Desperate mind, if it's the limit, we can rewrite it.
破壊と再生から 私ができる
From destruction and rebirth, I can make it.
ギリギリ愛 いけないボーダーライン
Desperate love, the forbidden borderline,
難易度Gでも全て壊してみせる
even at difficulty G, I'll smash it all.
ギリギリマインド さらにGへと
Desperate mind, pushing even further to G,
意識は溶ける 体は制御不能 行っちゃうかもね
consciousness melts, body out of control, I might go!
ギリギリ愛 いけないボーダーライン
Desperate love, the forbidden borderline,
燃え尽きながら まだ輝いてみせる
while burning out, I'll still shine bright.
ギリギリマインド あなたのために
Desperate mind, for your sake,
未来のために 何度砕け散っても
for the future, no matter how many times I shatter,
愛することで 生まれ変わる
by loving, I am reborn.
愛されたくて 生きて帰る
I want to be loved and live to return.
ギリギリ愛 いけないボーダーライン
Desperate love, the forbidden borderline,
難易度Gでも全て壊してみせる
even at difficulty G, I'll smash it all.
ギリギリマインド さらにGへと
Desperate mind, pushing even further to G,
意識は溶ける 体は制御不能 行っちゃうかもね
consciousness melts, body out of control, I might go!
ギリギリ愛 あなたのために
Desperate love, for your sake,
未来のために 何度砕け散っても
for the future, no matter how many times I shatter,
愛することで 生まれ変わる
by loving, I am reborn.
愛されたくて 生きて帰る
I want to be loved and live to return.
愛されたくて
Wanting to be loved,
生きてる
I am alive.
どうだった？
How was it?
なんかすごい、ちょっとどんな感じか持ってきちゃったけど、すごい、すごいステージだった！
I was wondering what kind of vibe it would be, but it was such an amazing stage!
すごいステージだった！
Such an amazing stage!
どう？聞こえる？
How is it? Can you hear me?
すごい、なんか、すごいよ！みんな！すごい、ありがとう！
Wow, it's amazing, everyone! Thank you so much!
本当にさ、
Truly,
もうこうやってな、こういうふうにな、
being able to, like this,
こういう、ちょっと語彙力が、語彙力が、こういうステージでな、
in a vocabulary... I mean, on a stage like this,
歌えるのは本当にみんなのおかげだって本当に思います、本当にありがとうございます。
singing here is truly thanks to everyone. Thank you so much.
本当にね、もう、とはね、結構ワールドワイドな感じで、
Truly, Towa is pretty worldwide,
うん、本当に、もういっぱいいろんなね、国のコメントがあって、とっても嬉しいです！みんなありがとう！
yeah, truly, there are comments from all sorts of countries, I'm so happy! Thank you everyone!
イヤー、みんな見てる？ありがとう！本当に嬉しい！
Yay, are you all watching? Thank you! I'm so happy!
てかさ、動きがさ、うるさくてさ、
And you know, my movements are so noisy,
と、と、と、と、と、と、と、と、と！
and to-to-to-to-to-to-to-to!
いけないボーダーライン、どうだった？分かった？
How was "Ikenai Borderline"? Did you like it?
こちらこそ、あ、ありがとう！サンキュー！
I should be saying that. Ah, thank you! Thank you!
いけないボーダーライン、すごくかっこいいよね！いつかさ、これもね、歌ってあげたいななんてちょっとと思ってます！
"Ikenai Borderline" is so cool, right? Someday, I'd love to sing this for you too, I've been thinking.
はーい！
Yeah!
まあいいか、な。ちょっと、次のな、もう一回でもいけないボーダーラインですごい盛り上がったんで、
Well, that's fine. Next, since "Ikenai Borderline" got everyone so hyped up,
次は、あ、とはお水が飲みたい！
next is... ah, Towa wants some water!
急に、急に、お水が飲みたい。
Suddenly... suddenly, I want to drink water.
お水って大事だよね。お水って。
Water is important, right? Water.
てかさ、もしかしてマイペースなんだよね、そう。多分さ、あのさ、今日初めて見たよって方もしょ、いると思うんですけど、と、も結構配信とかでもマイペースなんですよ、な、とは。
And you know, maybe I'm at my own pace. Yeah, probably, there are people watching for the first time today, but Towa is quite at her own pace even in streams.
まあ、でもそのマイペースなこと、と、も、みんな好きでいてくれてるの本当、ありがとう！ありがとう！
Well, but you all love that about me, thank you so much! Thank you!
クー！ちょっともう一回飲もう。
Kuu! Let's drink once more.
じゃあ次はね、なんか静かな、ゆったりとした曲を歌おうかなって思ってます。
Next, I thought I'd sing a quiet, relaxing song.
ちょっと疲れちゃった時にね、聴いてくれたらなって、聴くとね、元気が出る曲、とははすごい好き。
When you're feeling tired, if you listen to it, it gives you energy—Towa really loves songs like that.
はい、まあポケモンのね、曲なんですけども、そこに空があるから。
Yes, well, it's a Pokémon song, "Soko ni Sora ga Aru Kara".
振向いてごらん 君のつけた道が
Turn and look at the road you've followed,
顔上げてごらん 未来を創るよ
Lift up your head and look, you're creating the future!
頑張ることに 疲れたときには
When you've become tired from trying so hard,
空を見上げて 涙を流そう
Look to the sky and let your tears flow.
頑張ることに 疲れたときには
When you've become tired from trying so hard,
空を見上げて 涙を流そう
Look to the sky and let your tears flow.
頬撫でる風が きっと言うから
The wind will brush your cheeks; I'm sure it'll say,
「転んでもいいさ 君は君がすきさ」
"It's ok to fall. You are you, and that makes you wonderful."
傷つかぬ者に 青空は見えない
Those that haven't been hurt cannot see the blue sky
迷い歩むたび 生命は輝く
On a journey where you hesitate to walk on, your life will shine
どんな笑顔で 包んであげたら
With what kind of smile should I embrace you
君のかなしみ 癒せるだろう
to heal your sorrow?
雲の隙間から 見える太陽
The sun visible through the gaps in the clouds
照らし始めるよ 真っ直ぐなその瞳
begins to shine into your straight eyes.
見つめてごらん 向かい風の向こうに
Look at the other side of the wind
描き続けている 未来が待っている
And continue to draw the future that is waiting for you!
どんな笑顔で 包んであげたら
With what kind of smile should I embrace you
君のかなしみ 癒せるだろう
to heal your sorrow?
さあ、始めようか
Let's start...
振り返ってごらん 君のつけた道が
Now turn around and look at the path you've made.
顔上げてごらん 未来を創るよ
Raise your head up and look, we'll create the future.
頑張ることに疲れたときには
Whenever you get tired of trying your hardest,
空を見上げて涙を流そう
Look up at the sky and let your tears flow.
頬なでる風がきっと言うから
The wind brushing against your cheek will surely tell you:
「転んでもいいさ 君は君がすてきさ」
"It's okay to fall, you're wonderful just as you are."
傷つかぬ者に青空は見えない
Those who haven't been hurt cannot see the blue sky.
迷い歩むたび生命は輝く
Every time we wander and walk, life shines bright.
どんな笑顔で包んであげたら
With whatever smile I wrap around you,
君の悲しみ癒せるだろう
It will surely heal your sorrow.
雲の隙間から見える太陽
The sun visible between the clouds
照らし始めるよまっすぐなその瞳
begins to shine through your straightforward eyes.
見つめてごらん向かい風の向こうに
Look across the headwind,
描き続けている未来が待ってる
the future we continue to draw is waiting for us.
歩いて行こうそこに空があるから
Let's walk on, because the sky is there.
そこに空があるからでしたー！
Because there is a sky up there, that's why!
けっこうけっこうだって、けっこう！ふふっ！
Quite a bit, quite a bit, quite a bit... Heh!
あー
Ah.
ちょっとな、この曲けっこうな、好きでな、そう。
Well, you know, I really like this song, right?
そう、でも、なんかね、そうちょっと疲れたときとかって、
And you know, when you get really tired,
下に向かってしまうと思うんだけど、そのときにね、空を見上げてね、ゆっくりしたら、いいんじゃないかな、みたいなの。
you probably look up at the sky and calm down, right?
いぇーい！
Yay!
あ、お水飲んでいい？
Should I drink some water?
のろ…
Drink...
ねえ、いっぱいコメント見てるよ！
Yeah, I'm reading lots of comments!
とわーたん、とわーたん。
Towatan... Towatan...
なんかWから始まる言葉いっぱいなんじゃないのこれ？もしかして。
Are there lots of words starting with "W"? Maybe?
つーわけね、だいじ！最高だった！ありがとう、TMT！
TMT is the best, thank you, TMT!
なんですかTMTって、やめてくださいね本当に。
What is TMT? Don't ask me that, seriously!
もう、TMDですから！
Come on, it's TMD!
トワさまマジ大悪魔！
Towa-sama is a serious archdemon!
そう、あ、TM、あ、TMA！
So, ah, TM, ah, TM...
トワさまマジ大悪魔、そう。
Towa-sama is seriously an archdemon, yeah.
いやー、どうしような。
Yeah, what should I do?
なんかな、もうなんか感動だよな。
I'm just so moved, you know?
ねえ、もうな、もう早いことに、もう1時間経っちゃいますよ。
Right? It's already been an hour since it started.
終わりに近づいてきましたよ。
We're getting close to the end.
もうすごい良い思い出でしたよ、これは。
It was such a good memory, wasn't it? This was.
いい思い出でした、いい思い出ですよ。
It was a good memory, it was a good memory!
でさ、なんかね、あれだから、なんかでも、恥ずかしくてアーカイブ見れるかな、トワさま？
Well, because it's... you know, I wonder if I can watch the archive, Towa-sama?
アーカイブ見れるかな？ドキドキ。
Can I watch the archive? Dokidoki.
でもいっぱいの人がね、見てくれて、トレンドもね、1位になったみたいで、
Lots of people watched and we were even number one in trends!
とっても嬉しいです！ありがとうございます！
I'm so happy, thank you very much!
みんなのおかげだよ、君たちのおかげだよ。
It's all thanks to you guys, thanks to you all!
じゃあね、ちょっとね、告知をさせていただきます！あとなんだ、さっき、こっち、体を見せたときに、最後に帽子見せたじゃん？その帽子のこの缶バッジが発売されることになりましたー！じゃーん！
Let me make an announcement one more time. Earlier, when I showed my body, I showed my hat, right? The hat's badge is going to be sold! Tada!
トワさまのピースのアクリルスタンドとこの缶バッジセット、
Towa-sama's Peace acrylic stand and badge set.
ぜひぜひ！このね、配信が終わったあとに、缶バッジが、トワさま恐れになっちゃうからつけたら！つけてれ！つけてれ！つけてれ！つけてる恐れに…ちょっぴりこきききききーっ！って、そういう感じでね。
Please, please! Once this stream ends, I'm going to attach the badge because I'll be scared of Towa-sama... I'll attach it! I'll attach it! I'll attach it because I'll be scared of Towa-sama... *giggle* Something like that, you know?
ちょっと語彙力、誰か辞書持ってきて！誰かトワの後ろで辞書してよ！
Wait, someone bring a dictionary! Does anyone know the dictionary behind Towa?
かわいいでしょ？ よかったらみなさん買っていきなさーい。
Isn't it cute? If you'd like, everyone, please buy one.
帽子もね。
The hat too.
まあ、帽子は、まあ、まあ、まあ、まあ、まあ、まあ。
Well, the hat is, well, well, well, well, well, well.
うふ、うふとか言って（笑）
Heh, saying things like that (laughs).
待って、この髪の、髪もかわいいのよ。
Wait, this hair, the hair is cute too.
これこれ、この帽子のお揃いだよ。
Look, look, it's matching with this hat.
これ買ったらお揃いになるよ、これ。
If you buy this, it matches, this.
あれ何これ？小指が小指じゃん、いや。
What's this? That's a pinky, no.
これよ、これとこれ、ほら、ほれ。
This, this and this, see, look.
そう、可愛いでしょう？
Right? Cute, isn't it?
で、この後、配信終わった30分後ですね。
And, after this, 30 minutes after the stream ends,
9時半に、あのnikiさんの「ERROR」という曲を歌ったんです。
at 9:30, I sang a song called "ERROR" by niki-san.
イラストは、カガミテンテンにお願いして描いてもらいましたー！
I asked Kagami Tenten to draw the illustration!
めちゃめちゃかっこよくない？これ。
Isn't this super cool? This.
神絵師よ。
An artist god.
これ超かっこいいよなー！カガミテンテンに描いてもらった。
This is super cool! Drawn by Kagami Tenten.
もう本当に、ま、出難いですよ。動画もね、めちゃくちゃかっこいいんで。
Really, it's hard to put into words. The video is super cool too.
もうみんなですごい「あれやこれや」と言いながらね、作った一つ一つの作品なんですよ。
Everyone worked hard making every single piece of work.
1作品になるので、よかったら見てくださーい！
It turns into one work, so please check it out!
じゃあね、それをね、今から水を飲んだ後に歌わせてもらいますよ。
Well then, I'll sing that after drinking some water.
緊張しちゃって、体力なくなっちゃうからね。
Getting nervous makes me lose stamina.
じゃあこの、この後、これ、あ、今歌います。
So, after this, this, ah, I'll sing it now.
じゃあ、nikiさんのね、ERROR聞いてください。
Well then, please listen to niki-san's "ERROR".
見える?この目の涙
Can you see? Through these tears
命の色に滲んでいる
The colors of life are blurring
何を残して与えた?
What are you leaving behind?
問いかけて 壊れて
Calling out, I'm collapsing
青と赤と白 混ざるこの世の中で
Blue, red, and white blurring within this world
叫んでいる
I'm shouting
何を求めて歩いた?
What are you looking for?
追いかけて 疲れて どのくらい異常?
Chasing, it's tiring. When will it end?
壊れているの?
Am I breaking down?
壊れているよ
I am breaking!
それでも 息を…したい
Even still, I want to keep... breathing
君に見えてるの?
Did I just see you?
夢のように最後の 言葉も詰まるよ
Like in the last dream? Even the words are blocked
ERROR
遠い日のこと 柔い光が 空に溢れている
On a distant day a faint light is flooding the sky
何を選んで並べた? 涙色 重ねて
What have you decided on? Tears are welling up
浮かぶその身体 意識の中 溶けて 滲んでしまう
Afloat, the consciousness in that body is melting and blurring
何を見てきて 比べた?
What are you comparing it to?
悲しくて 忘れて どのくらい異常?
It's sad, I've forgotten. When will it end?
歪んでいるの?
Is it distorted?
歪んでいるよ
It is distorted!
それでも 息を…したい
Even still, I want to keep... breathing
夢を見ているの 想う君に 最後の 言葉も詰まるよ
Am I dreaming? Is this the last thought of you? Even the words are blocked
ERROR
与えることも 失うことも 忘れることも できないの?
Even if I give, even if I lose, even if I forget, can't I?
暴れだす この エラー
I'm restless, kill this error
殺して 笑う 僕 がまた エラー
Laughing I still haven't error
壊しているの? 壊して知るのか?
Am I broken? Do you know what's broken?
それでも 涙 …イタイ 痛い
Even still the tears... hurt, hurt
君に届いたの?
Have I reached you?
歌う声に 最後の 言葉並べても
With my last singing voice? Even the lined up words
重なる色 滲んで
Overlapping colors are blurring
壊れているの?
Am I breaking down?
壊れているよ
I am breaking!
それでも 息を…したい
Even still, I want to keep... breathing
君に見えてたの?
Did I just see you?
夢のように最後の 言葉も詰まるよ
Like in the last dream? Even the words are blocked
ERROR
それでも涙
Even so, tears
いたい
hurt...
君に届いたの
Did it reach you?
歌う声に最後の言葉並べても
Even if I line up my final words in song,
重なる色滲んで
overlapping colors blur.
壊れているの
Am I breaking down?
壊れているよ
I am breaking down.
それでも息を
Even still, breath...
したい したい
I want to, want to...
君に見えてたの
Were you seeing it?
夢のように最後の言葉も詰まるよ
Like a dream, even my final words choke up.
error
常闇トワ 3Dお披露目
Tokoyami Towa 3D Debut